<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>6.5.2 SIM Manage on</title><link>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/</link><description>Recent content in 6.5.2 SIM Manage on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 15:09:40 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>6.5.2 Sim manage</title><link>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/sim-card/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:05:28 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/sim-card/</guid><description>SIM manage # -SIM Card Manager helps to manage all SIM card related issues with easy functions for managers. For details, please see items below.
1.1 Add Sim # Step 1: Click on Add Sim. Step 2: A dialog box appears: Account: Select the account to add a SIM.
Download template: Download the sample file format.
Select document: Upload CCID self-fill file.</description></item><item><title>6.5.2.3 Report SIM expire</title><link>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/sim-report/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:06:25 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/sim-report/</guid><description>Report SIM expire # Report SIM expire to output a list of expired SIMs on the system. Help managers easily statistics and renew SIM. Search # Step 1: You can search by the following criteria: CCID: Enter SIM CCID, can enter 1 or more characters. SIMNO: Enter SIM phone number, can enter 1 or more characters. SIM type: Select the type of SIM to search.</description></item><item><title>6.5.2.4 Fee by Type</title><link>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/fee-by-type/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 13:56:26 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/fee-by-type/</guid><description>Fee by type # Fee by type to output the total quantity, service charge by type of SIM and the total service cost over the total number of SIMs. Search # Step 1: You can search by the following criteria: Date: Select the time period to search SIM type: Select SIM service type. Sub account: Click on if you want to search on the child account.</description></item><item><title>6.5.2.5 Fee Sim</title><link>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/fee-sim/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 13:57:31 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/fee-sim/</guid><description>Fee SIM # Fee SIM to output the unit price for each number, each type of SIM. Search # Step 1: You can search by the following criteria: Date: Select the time period to search. CCID: Enter the CCID number sequence, can enter 1 or more characters. SIMNO: Enter your phone number, you can enter 1 or more characters. SIM type: Select the SIM service type.</description></item><item><title>6.5.2.6 Fee Import by Type</title><link>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/fee-import-by-type/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 13:58:17 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/fee-import-by-type/</guid><description>Fee import by type # Fee import by type to output a total cost report on the number of SIMs newly added to the SIM store. Categorize costs by quantity and unit price of each type of SIM. Search # Step 1: You can search by the following criteria: Date: Select the time period to search. SIM type: Select the SIM service type. Sub account: Click on if you want to search on the child account.</description></item><item><title>6.5.2.7 Fee Import Sim</title><link>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/fee-import-sim/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 13:58:37 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/fee-import-sim/</guid><description>Fee import SIM # Fee import SIM to output the unit price for each number, each type of SIM. Search # Step 1: You can search by the following criteria: Date: Select the time period to search. CCID: Enter the CCID number sequence, can enter 1 or more characters. SIMNO: Enter your phone number, you can enter 1 or more characters. SIM type: Select the SIM service type.</description></item><item><title>6.5.2.8 Activity Summary</title><link>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/activity-summary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:07:28 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/activity-summary/</guid><description>Activity summary # Activity summary historical statistics, SIM management status by date. Search # Step 1: You can search by the following criteria: Date: Select the time period to search. Sub account: Click on if you want to search on the child account. Step 2: Click Search to display the results or click Reset to reset to default.</description></item><item><title>6.5.2.9 Log Change</title><link>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/history-change/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:10:10 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/history-change/</guid><description>Log change # Log change to output change history reports, per SIM activity. Search # Step 1: You can search by the following criteria: Date: Select the time period to search. Actions: Select any function, SIM related activities. CCID: Enter the CCID number sequence, can enter 1 or more characters. SIMNO: Enter your phone number, you can enter 1 or more characters. SIM type: Select the SIM service type.</description></item><item><title>6.5.2.10 Check Fee</title><link>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/fee-check/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:09:28 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/fee-check/</guid><description>Check fee # Check fee to output the status report, the service term of the SIM corresponding to / is not being bundled with the device. Search # Step 1: You can search by the following criteria: CCID: Enter the CCID number sequence, can enter 1 or more characters. SIMNO: Enter your phone number, you can enter 1 or more characters. SIM type: Select the type of SIM to search.</description></item><item><title>6.5.2.11 Report Extend</title><link>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/report-extend/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 16:32:06 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://help.gotrack365.com/en/platform/manage/warehouse/sim-manage/report-extend/</guid><description>Report Extend # Report Extend to output the list of expired SIMs and the total amount of SIM renewal on the system. Search # Step 1: You can search by the following criteria: Date: Select the time period to search. CCID: Enter the CCID number sequence, can enter 1 or more characters. SIMNO: Enter your phone number, you can enter 1 or more characters. SIM type: Select the type of SIM to search.</description></item></channel></rss>